USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
AZ 517
This collection contains papers, photographs, objects, and memorabilia of the USS Arizona from its christening in 1915 to destruction on December 7, 1941. Also held within the collection are materials documenting the annual memorial ceremonies held at the University of Arizona Student Union and the papers of the USS Arizona Reunion Association.
16 linear feet.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
Box 46 items 2a, 3a, 4a, 5a are restricted.
Historical Note
The USS Arizona (BB-39) was launched by the United States Navy on June 19, 1915 and later commissioned on October 17, 1916. The ship was the second and last ship of the Pennsylvania class of super dreadnought battleships and boasted a 608 foot long hull made of steel which at its maximum breath reached 97 feet. She remained in the United States during World War I and instead served as a gunnery training ship on Chesapeake Bay. Following the end of World War I, she departed for Britain. On December 12, 1918 the ship sailed from Portsmouth, England acting as escort for President Woodrow Wilson to the Paris Peace Conference in Brest, France. In early 1919 the US Navy sent the ship to the Mediterranean on a few months' cruise. In 1921 the ship was sent into the Pacific to join the United States Pacific Fleet. From 1929-1931, the ship was modernized and used for training exercises between the two World Wars. The USS Arizona was used as aid to survivors of the Long Beach, CA earthquake of 1933. By 1940, the ship was a part of the Pacific Fleet that was transferred from California to Pearl Harbor, HI to deter imperialist Japanese forces. It was while stationed here that the USS Arizona was bombed during the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor on December 7, 1941, which resulted in the death of 1,177 officers and crewmen and the sinking of the ship. The wreckage of the ship is at the bottom of Pearl Harbor and the USS Arizona Memorial, dedicated on May 30, 1962, straddles the ship's hull.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series.
Series I:Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
Subseries 1: Negatives, undated
Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1940
Subseries 3: 8x10 Photographs, 1915-1962
Subseries 3: Oversize Materials, 1920 – 1941 December 7
Series II: Documents, 1907-2000
Series III: Objects, circa 1911-1983
Series IV: Audio Visual Materials, 1981-1984
Series V: USS Arizona Reunion Association, Crew-Kin and Related Materials, 1931-2015
Subseries 1: Documents, 1960-2007
Subseries 2: Photographs, 1931-2002
Subseries 3: Oral History Transcriptions, 1981-2001
Subseries 4: Correspondence, 1984-2006
Subseries 5: Objects, 1971
Subseries 6: Audiovisual Materials, 1934-1994
Subseries 7: Lauren F. Bruner Materials, 2013-2015
Series VI: Appendices
Scope and Content Note
This is an artificial collection comprised of materials gifted by various donors. The collection contains materials documenting the USS Arizona from its christening in June 19, 1915 to destruction on December 7, 1941. Also included are materials that document annual memorial ceremonies held at the University of Arizona Student Union and the papers of the USS Arizona Reunion Association.
The collection is comprised of six series. The first series has four subseries and comprises the bulk of the collection. This series contains photographic materials taken by the ship's personnel, the United States Navy, and other entities that document the history of the ship during its lifespan. Materials document the ship's crew, its arsenal and machinery, the various locales where the ship was stationed or provided aid, as well as other US Navy ships. Also included are materials that document the ship's interior and exterior, the December 7, 1941 Japanese attack at Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, and the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii.
The second series contains documents that detail the history of the ship and the lives of her crew as well as materials documenting the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. Materials within this series include books; programs for sporting events, religous services, and other activities on board ship; cards; invitations; certificates; ship logs; crew rosters; listings of crew and personnel; as well as USS Arizona Memorial materials; and copies of the At Em' Arizona newsletter and other materials that were generated during the ship's lifespan. Also contained in this series are scrapbooks by various sailors who served on the ship. These scrapbooks date from the 1929-1955 and contain black and white photographs, documents, and ephemera that detail the history of the USS Arizona and other US Navy battleships and the United States involvement in World War II.
The third series contains objects that resided on the ship as well as memorial and commemorative objects. The fourth series contains audio visual materials and is comprised of cassette tapes of oral histories with sailors who served on the USS Arizona as well as VHS tapes of USS Arizona memorial ceremonies.
The fifth series has seven subseries and consists of materials created by the USS Arizona Reunion Association and USS Arizona Crew-Kin Association, which are comprised of individuals who served on the USS Arizona and their kin. The sixth series contains appendices which hold access copies of documents and photographs held within the collection.
Some Materials from this collection are on permanent exhibit as part of the USS Arizona Exhibit located at the University of Arizona Student Union Memorial Center.
For more information, see Digital Exhibit.
For more photographs of the USS Arizona, see collections held at the U.S. Naval Institute, USS Arizona Memorial Collection held by the National Park Service, the National Archives, and the Naval Historical Center, NH.
Access Terms
United States. Navy – History – 20th century—Sources.
USS Arizona Reunion Association.
Arizona (Battleship) -- History.
World War, 1939-1945 –Personal narratives, American.
Battleships—United States—History—Sources.
World War, 1939-1945—Campaigns—Hawaii--Sources.
World War, 1939-1945--Naval operations, American.
Pearl Harbor (Hawaii), Attack on, 1941—Pictorial works.
USS Arizona Memorial (Hawaii)--Sources..
At 'Em Arizona
Container List
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  This series has four subseries and comprises the bulk of the collection and contains photographic materials taken by the ship's personnel and the United States Navy that document the crew of the ship, the daily lives and duties of sailors who served on the ship, interior and exterior views of the ship and its armament, and the various locales where the ship was stationed, held port, or provided aid. Also included in this series are materials that document the Neptune’s Court Ceremony, the 1934 filming of the motion picture Here Comes the Navy featuring James Cagney and Gloria Stewart, and the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, Hawaii on December 7, 1941. Certain materials are copies of original photographs held at the National Archives, The National Park Service USS Arizona Memorial, the Naval Historical Center, NH, the U.S. Naval Institute, and other collections. The majority of the materials are undated, but are believed to date circa 1920-1941. Item titles contain an accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
  - Subseries 1: Negatives, undated
    This subseries is arranged numerically by accession number and is described at the item level. It contains copy negatives of photographs held within the collection. Item titles contain an accession number assigned by the Arizona State Museum upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
    - 50-1-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 50-1-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 54-1-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 55-3-3A, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 55-3-3B, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 58-3-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 58-3-4, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 58-7-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 62-1-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 63-3-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 63-3-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 64-1-5, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 64-6-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 66-1-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 67-4-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 67-4-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 68-1-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 68-4-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 68-5-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 68-5-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 68-6-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 68-9-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 71-4-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 71-4-3, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 71-4-8, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 73-2-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 73-2-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 73-2-3, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 76-6-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 77-2-1A, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 77-3-5, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 77-3-33, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 77-4-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 77-4-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 77-4-3, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 77-4-4, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 77-5-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 77-5-2, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 77-6-1, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 77-7-1, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 77-7-2, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 84-4-1, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 84-10-1, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 84-11-1A, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 84-11-1B, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 84-14-1A, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 84-14-1B, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 84-14-1C, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 84-26-1, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 84-26-2, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 84-26-3, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 84-26-4, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 84-26-5, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 84-26-6, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 84-26-7, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 84-26-9, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 84-26-10, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 84-26-8, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 84-26-64, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 84-26-100, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 84-26-104, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 84-26-105, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 84-26-106, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 84-26-107, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 84-26-110, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 84-26-111, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 84-26-112, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 84-27-1A, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 84-27-1B, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 84-27-1C, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 84-27-1D, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 84-27-2A, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 84-27-2B, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 84-27-2C, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 84-27-3, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 84-27-4, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 84-27-5, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 84-27-6, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 84-27-7, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 84-27-8, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 84-27-9, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 84-27-10, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 84-27-11, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 84-27-12, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 84-27-13, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 84-27-14, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 84-27-15, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 84-27-16, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 84-27-17, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 84-27-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 84-27-19, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 84-27-20, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 84-28-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 84-28-2, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 84-28-3, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 84-28-4, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 84-28-5, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 84-28-6, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 84-28-7, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 84-28-8, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 84-28-9, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 84-28-10, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 84-28-11, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 84-28-12, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 84-28-13, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 84-28-14, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 84-28-15, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 84-28-16, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 84-28-17, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 84-29-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 84-29-2, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 84-29-3, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 84-29-4, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 84-29-5, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 84-29-6, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 84-29-7, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 84-29-8, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 84-29-9, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 84-29-10, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 84-29-11, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 84-29-12, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 84-29-13, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 84-29-14, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 84-29-15, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 84-29-16, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 84-29-17, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 84-31-2, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 1918 USS Arizona Crew, 85-1-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 85-4-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 85-4-2, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - 85-4-3, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 85-4-4, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 85-4-5, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 85-4-6, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 85-4-7, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 85-4-8, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 85-4-9, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 85-4-10, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - 85-4-11, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - 85-6-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - 85-6-2, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - 85-9-5, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - 87-2-1, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1941
    This subseries comprises the bulk of this series and is arranged numerically by accession number. Items within this subseries are described at the item level. Certain materials are duplicated in other series within the collection. Materials consist primarily of black and white photographs of varying size that document the interior and exterior of the ship, its armament and machinery, the USS Arizona and other US Navy battleships stationed at various ports, the ship and her crew engaging in training exercises on the ship and on base, the ship in dry dock at various ports, and other scenarios. Materials within this subseries also document the crew and individual sailors engaging in routine duties as well as personal activities while on ship leave. Materials of particular interest from this subseries document the 1933 Long Beach, California earthquake relief efforts, the ship sailing the Panama Canal, the Neptune's Court Ceremony, the 1934 filming of Here Comes the Navy featuring James Cagney and Gloria Stewart, various USS Arizona athletic teams, and the December 7, 1941 Japanese attack at Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. Undated materials are believed to date circa 1920-1941. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-1, 1916 November 11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-2, 1916 November 18 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-3, 1916 November 25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-4, 1916 December 02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-5, 1916 December 09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-6, 1916 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-8, 1916 December 23 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-8, 1916 December 30 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-9, 1917 January 06 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-10, 1917 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-11, 1917 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-12, 1917 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-13, 1917 June 24 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-14, 1917 February 03 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - USS Arizona Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Phillip H. Smith, Paterson, NJ, 63-2-15, 1917 April 18 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Bow of Ship from Observation Tower, 84-37-1, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Bow of Ship from Observation Tower, 84-37-1, copy, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bow of Ship, 84-37-2, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Bow of Ship, 84-37-2, copy, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-3, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-3, copy, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - At Sea, 84-37-4, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - At Sea, 84-37-4, copy, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Rear of Ship, 84-37-5, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Wave Hitting Ship, 84-37-6, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-7, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-8, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-9, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-10, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-11, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Wave Hitting Bow, 84-37-12, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Sailor Doing Laundry on Deck, 84-37-13, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Sailors Scrubbing Deck, 84-37-14, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Sailors Sweeping Deck, 84-37-15, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Laundry Hanging, 84-37-16, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Sweeping Deck, 84-37-17, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Sailors Airing Bedding on Deck, 84-37-18, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Sailor Getting Into Uniform on Deck, 84-37-19, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified Sailors on Deck, 84-37-20, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Sailor Working On Land, 84-37-21, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified Sailors Sunning on Deck, 84-37-22, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified Sailors on Pier, 84-37-23, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Sailors in Dress on Deck, 84-37-24, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Sailors on Deck Near Lifeboat, 84-37-25, circa 1936 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Ed Soja and Unidentified Sailor on Beach, 84-37-26, circa 1935 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Sailor Life Cartoon, 84-37-27, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Front of Ship, 84-37-28, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Port Side of Ship as it Looked from Top of #2 Turret, 84-37-29, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - View of Bow from Tower, 84-37-30, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ship in Dress, 84-37-31, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - View of Ship in Dock, 84-37-32, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - View of Conning Tower, 84-37-33, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - View of Conning Tower, 84-37-34, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - View of Ship in Dock, 84-37-35, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - View of Unidentified Sailors on Conning Tower, 84-37-36, circa 1930 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - View of Conning Tower in Dock, 84-37-37, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - View of United States Flag on Deck, 84-37-38, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Brig, 84-37-39, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Standing in Marine Compartments Looking Toward Quarter Deck, 84-37-40, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Interior of Ship, 84-37-41, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Weapon Heads on Deck, 84-37-42, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Two Liberty Boats, 84-37-43, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - View of Ship in Dock, 84-37-44, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Plane on Catapult, 84-37-45, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Damaged Plane on Catapult, 84-37-46, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Damaged Plane on Catapult, 84-37-47, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Knot Specimen Board, 84-37-48, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Arizona Getting Her Belly Cleaned, Bremerton Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 84-37-49, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Los Angeles River, 84-37-50, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bridge Over Los Angeles River in Long Beach, CA, 84-37-51, circa 1937 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bridge Going Out Of Los Angeles River, Long Beach, CA, 1938, 84-37-52 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Bridge Washed Out By Los Angeles River, 1938, 84-37-53 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Pet Seal Near USS Arizona Anchorage, Long Beach Harbor, 84-37-54, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles River Food, Long Beach, CA, 1938, 84-37-55 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Los Angeles Bridge Going Out, Long Beach, CA, 1938, 84-37-56 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Los Angeles Bridge Flood, Long Beach, CA, 1938, 84-37-57 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Thirteen Unidentified Sailors in a Race Boat, 84-37-58, circa 1938 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Photograph of Thirteen Unidentified Sailors In Race Boat Taken from Bow, 84-37-59, circa 1938 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Boats Coming to shore, 84-37-60, circa 1938 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Harry Halman Posing with Car, California, circa 1930, 84-37-61 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Steve and a Pal in Hawaii, 84-37-62, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Neptune’s Court Ceremony, Administrating Anesthetic, Doctor and Attendants, Patient in Chair, Equator Crossing, 1936, 84-37-63 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Panama Canal, 84-37-64, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 84-37-65, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal with Sailors on Deck, 84-37-66, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal with Battleship in Background, 84-37-67, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal with Sailors on Deck Taken from Conning Tower, 84-37-68, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Bow of USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 84-37-69, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - At Em, Captain Baum's Dog, 1935-1936, 84-37-70 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Ship's Mascot, At Em, 1936, 84-37-71 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Part of U.S. Fleet Taken from Crow's Nest of USS Arizona, 1936, 84-37-72 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Part of U.S. Fleet Taken from Crow's Nest of USS Arizona, 1936, 84-37-73 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Part of U.S. Fleet Taken from Crow's Nest of USS Arizona, 1936, 84-37-74 (Box 5, Folder 48)